Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Thank you!
血潮に乗ってその身に纏ったクラウン
空になく全てを振り払うように
叶えよう約束通り 君は出た世界だ
Let's start this world, even I cannot drop this world
All I need is getting strong, we can catch the game
負けないでよ 目に厚させてよ
ほら 見方に変えてよ We can kiss the game
揺れしだすよ その通り その影は見ないでよ We can kiss the game
What? But you... I mean... You're... How? Why? What? I'm so confused
Did you not hear me?
What's happening? Nero's a bird and birds don't talk
So how in the heck are you talking to me right now?
The bird just spoke
It must be a spirit! A noble spirit!
Nero! What's going on here? Since when have you been a talker?
Wait, I know! I'm still asleep, aren't I?
Kindly pick your jaw up off the ground
I need a portal at once
Not only is the bird talking, now it's giving me orders too?
As it stands, the humans who are still possessed by elves may not be able to change back
Huh?
That's not the worst part
Anyway, I need you to escort me to the demon's bones immediately
Wow, weird day
Now we turn
One good cop deserves another
Tempest of Blades!
You ever heard of a fair fight, pal?
This devil's got some dirty tricks
Not only can he make anything he says manifest as magic
He can summon objects, move them, and manipulate them however he sees fit
That Tempest of Blades technique is pretty much all those things at once
This is ridiculous
He withered Charlotte's briars, healed himself, and messes with us in every other way he can think of
But since he hasn't straight up ordered us to die, that must mean he has some limitations
Damn it, this is such a pain in the ass
Charlotte!
It's Sharla!
Earlier
With our fights!
Not all of my briars were affected by his attack
Perhaps they were out of range?
His magic capacity might have been a factor as well
Could it be that he's putting such a massive amount of magic power into his words
That our own spells are being overwhelmed?
All we can do is weather his attacks while we try to figure out what his weakness is
I did notice one thing though
No matter what he says, his words can't block my dark magic
Yep, he jumped out of the way
Now I just gotta land a good hit on him
Not too bad
For someone who's essentially still asleep, you seem to be moving around quite a bit
He's right
He's right, Licht can't use his full power yet
For now, the fight appears balanced
But soon
Tempest of rage
There's no end of these damn things
Man, this freak is even stronger than I thought
In terms of raw power, he's got us all beat
I can't keep my magic going forever
And he looks like he hasn't even broken a sweat
I'm enjoying your company
It's good to have something to keep me busy
Inhabiting my own body and playing freely with my magic spells is enough to make my heart dance with happiness
I'm very grateful to you
And of course, you helped me obtain the five-leaf grimoire
Let's try it
I'll show you what devils are truly capable of
Word's all magic
Just when I think I've seen his worst move
He's got more
I am a being from another dimension
The likes of which you cannot begin to fathom
You're doomed
What the hell is happening?
Magic
Is it from the world of the dead?
Cut them off and they grow right back
Yep, we're screwed
What is that?
No idea
Even with spatial magic that was a long trip
Don't waste time
Okay, okay, I got it stupid bird
Take out the magic stones embedded within this monument
Hey, all the magic stones that were stolen by the eye of the midnight sun are inside this thing
Are you sure I can do that?
Make it quick
Now, place the stones into the statue
It's the first wizard king
Here goes
And now the eyes
Almost done
Place the stones into the statue.
It's the first wizard king.
Here goes.
And now the eyes.
Almost done.
No way!
What's happening?
Watch out!
Oh no!
What's wrong with our spells?
They're melting!
Dark cloaked! Black blade! Blood flash!
That monster!
This train of my magic and my physical strength!
Soon you'll be too weak to carry your sword!
I've just initiated a devastating spell that depletes the life force from all the touches!
And once it starts, there's no way to stop it!
Eventually, it'll devour all of existence!
Damn! This keeps getting more hopeless!
There's something coming toward us!
What is that stuff?
The devil's power!
Light magic! Light swords of conviction!
Wind magic! Tornado fan!
It's absorbing all of our spells!
It's not stopping! Stay back!
Gotcha!
Hasta!
I thought that would've killed me for sure!
Oh, thank goodness!
Anti-magic works against that too?
And he isn't even injured!
Guess it didn't feel like swallowing a loser with no magic!
This is so bizarre!
We are!
I'm fine, by the way! Thanks a lot!
Oh no!
I knew it!
There's even more of that eerie magic power hovering above us right now!
Which means the people in the other rooms are in danger too!
If anyone has the swiftness to get the possessed magic knights out,
we have to protect the Clover Kingdom from this threat without abandoning any of our own.
I'll go and assist everyone in the lower rooms.
You'd better come with me, Vermillion.
Yes, sir.
You three seem to understand the enemy and what's going on above more than I do.
If you can find a way to use Asta's anti-magic, Yuno's spirit magic,
and the elf's light magic in tandem with one another,
you should make it to the main chamber.
Get moving!
Right!
Now that your seal has finally been broken,
I'm assuming my own seal will be released as well.
Huh? Miro...
What a pathetic state you're in.
If only my spell had worked more completely.
No. Without your help, I couldn't return at all.
Huh?
It's good to see you again, my prince.
At long last.
You're the first Wizard King!
That statue! It was you the whole time?
And how did Nero...
No way! Nero, is that really you?
You look, um, kinda different!
Hello!
If I had known you were secretly a gorgeous young lady,
I would have asked you on a date forever ago!
But hey, there's no time like the present, right?
Yep, cool, got it.
I sense an otherworldly magic emanating from the Shadow Palace.
I see. He must have obtained a new body then.
Back to you guys! How'd you get here?
Long ago, she used her sealing magic to confine me within the statue when I was close to death.
So I've been sleeping.
Then tonight, with the help of the magic stones, I was able to return at least partially.
His mana's so calm, yet so powerful. It's even stronger than elf magic!
As for her...
The truth is, I spent five centuries living as a bird.
Uh, why are you holding my hand?
Sealing magic! Inverse release!
Sealing magic!
Huh?
Now then, wait for your friends!
And thank you for setting me free!
Ahhhh!
You've been waiting for five hundred years. I'm so sorry.
No.
The most important thing is that we make sure history doesn't repeat itself.
As a noble, I should have been a powerful mage, but my magic was only good for opening and closing things, so others looked on it with contempt.
And I was assigned to serve an eccentric prince, whose magic was amazing even for royalty.
He's probably a snob.
Why, hello there! You must be Sekre, right?
I'm sorry. I would have come to you, but I've been so buried in my research lately.
Tell me, what's your magic like?
But he wasn't what I imagined at all.
Sealing magic?
I've never heard of that before! It must be rare! You're so lucky!
How can we put it to use? Thinking about it is so exciting!
All it does is open and close locks. It's shameful.
Hey, don't say that! You're sealing yourself off from the possibilities.
I hope you don't think you just said something clever.
Aww.
Also, your clothes are strange.
What? But I made them myself. You don't like them?
More importantly…
Don't change the subject.
What is it you need? I'm supposed to be your servant, after all.
Hmm, good question.
Right now, I'm trying to make some magical tools.
Magical tools?
That's right. With these, even someone born without any magic can use all kinds of spells.
I think it'll be a good way to make our society more equal in the future.
Equal? You're dreaming.
It can be done, with the help of my magic items. I'm sure your ability will be a huge help in making them. I know. Can you seal magic into objects?
Um, yes.
Wow, really? That's perfect!
And so, I helped the Prince with his magical inventions.
I'd never met anyone else like him in my whole life. There were some members of his family who resented him, because of the progressive ideas that he championed.
But he didn't let that bother him. He remained strong and honest, never compromising his beliefs.
I've noticed that he and his sister, Lady Tetya, have been sneaking out of the castle quite a lot recently. What could they be doing here?
Huh? They're meeting with a group of elves? Phenomenal magic talent. Similar ideals. The same four-leaf grimoires. For the first time, the Prince had found a pier and licked the leader of the elves.
Let's foster understanding. Your elvish mana really is a remarkable thing. If we combine that with our own magic item technology, this land will be safer and more prosperous. Let's all work together, hand in hand.
His items stored and distributed magic, and their magic stones amplified spells by linking to another world. By combining his work with the elves' resources, the Prince developed magic item technology ever further, and the world he dreamed of where both races could live in harmony was becoming a reality.
He and Licked were best friends, and soon they would become family as well.
I'm sorry, Tetya, but it looks like I might have to arrive late to your wedding. Father has summoned me to the palace that day, and I can't refuse. I know you're disappointed that he and the others don't approve of this, but please, don't worry. I'm sure they'll come to understand someday.
Yes, and it's all right. Even if you're late to the ceremony, Licked and his family will be so pleased to see you there.
But, it's likely that even then, his plot was already in motion.
Why did Father call me here? We didn't mention the wedding to anyone, so it must be coincidence. I should hurry or I'll miss it. Where is he?
I'm here, Father. You wanted to speak with me?
Now, bye!
What's this? I'm trapped!
Good day, my prince!
Minister? No, that villainous mana doesn't belong to him. Who are you?
Who, me? Despair? Hatred? Disloyalty? Death? Any number of awful things, really. Use whatever name you prefer.
I've read about this being. A soul from the other world with evil mana. A devil. Where's my family?
Who knows? Perhaps they've gone to confront that other race that's plotting to use your unwitting princess to topple this entire kingdom, but that's only a guess.
Imagine how surprised the elves will be when a monster's act of human violence befalls that little wedding ceremony that only you were supposed to know was happening.
No! Let go! No!
What an impressive spell. That's why they call you the best. Unfortunately, I was prepared for that, so even you won't escape from those bonds so easily. As soon as I obtain my body and grimoire, I promise I'll come back to play with you again.
Wait! Help me! Isn't anyone here? Please! Prince! Thank goodness!
Oh no, what's that? I've been trapped by a devil. I knew you would never do such a thing. I'm not sure why, but the magic item we created was stolen.
Quick! Use your sealing magic! Get me out of these restraints!
Of course! Sealing magic! Inverse release!
Come on! Fly faster! Tetya! Licht! Hold on!
There's the device we made!
No!
That's... a five-leaf grimoire!
I knew it!
Knew what?
Deep inside.
I knew you weren't responding.
That's... a five-leaf grimoire!
I knew it!
Knew it!
Knew what?
I knew it.
Deep inside. I knew you weren't responsible.
Has he reclaimed control of his heart?
Please forgive me. I should never have harbored any suspicion of you, not for a second.
Don't bother resisting. It's too late now. Relinquish your body to me.
You are the future we all believed in. You represent hope.
What are you...
Right now, my body is filled with an overwhelming amount of negative mana.
I can't control myself, but we mustn't let that devil succeed.
No, Ligt.
In order to keep my body in power from falling under the influence of evil, I've absorbed even more negative magic.
The stones? He used the highest form of forbidden magic on his own body?
Stop it. You can't do this.
I'm sorry, but I have one last selfish request, and only you can grant it.
I beg of you.
This isn't the answer!
Lumiere.
I need you to kill me.
You kill me.
Let's go.